Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1728., 1903; 002074
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1592., 1967; 001938
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Unfinished - presumably 1871 but check; Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1367., 1971; 001713
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0917., 1974; 001263
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1359., 1976; 001705
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0362., 000708
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0363., 000709
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0364., 000710
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0369., 000715
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0371., 000717
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1862-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0372., 000718
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0376., 000722
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0377., 000723
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0380., 000726
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0383., 000729
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0386., 000732
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0394., 000740
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1886, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0395., 000741
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0396., 000742
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0397., 000743
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0398., 000744
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0402., 000748
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0406., 000752
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0409., 000755
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0411., 000757
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0414., 000760
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0416., 000762
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0417., 000763
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0418., 000764
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0420., 000766
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0421., 000767
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0422., 000768
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0423., 000769
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0425., 000771
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0430., 000776
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0432., 000778
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0434., 000780
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0435., 000781
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0436., 000782
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0440., 000786
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0443., 000789
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0444., 000790
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0446., 000792
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0447., 000793
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0449., 000795
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1895-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0453., 000799
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0456., 000802
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0457., 000803
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1861-1884, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0459., 000805
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1835?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0460., 000806
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0463., 000809
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1897-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0465., 000811
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0467., 000813
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0468., 000814
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0472., 000818
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0476., 000822
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0479., 000825
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0481., 000827
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0482., 000828
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0486., 000832
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0489., 000835
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1867-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0492., 000838
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0498., 000844
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0500., 000846
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0506., 000852
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0509., 000855
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0514., 000860
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1864-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0518., 000864
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0527., 000873
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0538., 000884
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1886-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0542., 000888
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0543., 000889
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0546., 000892
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0548., 000894
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0554., 000900
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1867; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0559., 000905
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file. This file inclcludes one page of an original letter to Marsh which may or may not be from Carter. Check the spelling vs that of the microfilm versions. MAT 10/21/2004; unadjusted date string=1872-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0560., 000906
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1870-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0561., 000907
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0563., 000909
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1872; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0572., 000918
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0573., 000919
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1884; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0577., 000923
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1886-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0578., 000924
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted author string=Chester, Albert H; unadjusted date string=1866-1867; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0581., 000927
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1872-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0584., 000930
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1882; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0585., 000931
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0586., 000932
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0592., 000938
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0593., 000939
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as photocopies and/or typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1873-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0596., 000942
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as photocopies and/or typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1873-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0597., 000943
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0598., 000944
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0600., 000946
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0602., 000948
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0604., 000950
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0606., 000952
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1883-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0608., 000954
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0610., 000956
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0612., 000958
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1870-1890, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0614., 000960
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0615., 000961
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1891-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0620., 000966
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0622., 000968
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0623., 000969
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0624., 000970
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0625., 000971
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1884; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0629., 000975
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0632., 000978
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0636., 000982
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0639., 000985
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0640., 000986
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0643., 000989
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0645., 000991
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1882; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0649., 000995
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0654., 001000
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0655., 001001
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1865-1895, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0657., 001003
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1897-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0658., 001004
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0659., 001005
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0660., 001006
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0664., 001010
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0665., 001011
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1898-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0666., 001012
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0669., 001015
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0670., 001016
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0673., 001019
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1859-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0674., 001020
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0677., 001023
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0681., 001027
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1970; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0687., 001033
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0689., 001035
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library. Some or all of the letters exist as typed transcriptions in the document file.; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0693., 001039
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1888-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0699., 001045
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0706., 001052
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1879; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0708., 001054
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0710., 001056
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0712., 001058
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1886; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0713., 001059
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0718., 001064
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0719., 001065
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0722., 001068
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0724., 001070
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.0725., 001071